[音樂]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas：這兩個系統RQ和JSCheck，
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Both of these systems RQ and JSCheck,
最大限度地利用閉合和繼續。
make tremendous use of closure and continuation.
與閉合和延續一起工作的真正偉大之處在於
And the really great thing about working with closure and continuation
當你注意到這一點時，它們會讓你覺得自己很聰明。
is that they make you feel really smart when you notice this right.
昨天，你為結案做了很多工作，
Yesterday, that you've been doing a lot of work with closure,
當你拿到這些東西的時候，你會覺得自己很聰明，就像，嗯。
it makes you feel smart when you get these things, it's like, mm.
所以，每個人都應該有這種感覺，但你知道，那些做了很多事情的人
So and everybody deserves to feel that way yet you know how people who do a lot of
函數語言程式設計總是表現得像他們比你聰明得多？
functional programming are always acting like they're so much smarter than you are?
他們不是，但是他們一直在和這些東西打交道
They're not, but they're working with this stuff all the time and
這會讓他們一直感覺很好。
it makes them feel good all the time.
這讓他們覺得自己很聰明，這真的是一種很好的感覺，
It makes them feel smart and that's a really good way to feel,
每個人都應該有這樣的感覺。
everybody should feel like that.
而你每天工作的東西會讓你覺得自己很聰明嗎？
Whereas the stuff you're working with every day, does it make you feel smart?
不不是的。
No it does not.
所以你想要拿到這些東西，這很棒。
So you want to get a hold of this stuff, and it's great.
所以這兩個專案都是公共領域，都在GitHub上。
So both of these projects are public domain, they're both on GitHub.
他們都是完全免費的，如果他們能幫你去拿的話會有很多
They're both totally free, if they can help you go ahead and take it there's lots
世界上其他的好東西，如果它更適合你的話，也可以用它。
of other good stuff in the world too if that is better suited to you use that.
那麼，還有關於RQ、JSCheck或同步性的最後問題嗎？
So any last questions about RQ or JSCheck or synchronicity?
是?
Yes?
&gt；&gt；演講者2：這裡有幾個人在排隊。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: There's a couple that queued up here.
第一，他在想你是不是
One, he was wondering if you,
因為型別推斷與Hasko相同，所以您簽出Elm了嗎？
have you checked out Elm since the type inference is the same as Hasko?
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：是的，我之前提到過榆樹，有很多好東西。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah, I mentioned Elm earlier, there's good stuff.
名單上的一切都很好，但我想你會對我們的佇列感興趣，
Everything in that list is good, but I think our queue is of interest to you,
因為我認為它最適合您必須實施的工作流。
because it is the best suited, I think, to the workflows that you have to implement.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：還有別的嗎？
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Anything else?
&gt；&gt；演講者2：有一個來自安全部門。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: There's one from earlier from the security section.
他只是想讓你澄清，或者他在問，
He just wanted you to clarify, or he's asking,
我們正在學習安全中的物體以及如何防止攻擊，但是
we're learning about objects in security and how to prevent attacks but
這不是伺服器應該處理的事情嗎？
isn't this something that servers are supposed to deal with?
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：這是每件事都必須處理的事情，不是這樣的
&gt;&gt; Douglas: It's something everything has to deal with, it's not so
很多伺服器，都是我們。
much the servers, it's us.
我們要處理的是執行這些專案的人。
It's the people running the programs we have to deal with the stuff.
&gt；&gt；演講者3：是的，不過說得更具體一點。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yeah, a little bit more specifically, though.
聽起來我們在談論，你有一個物體
It sounds like we're talking about, you have an object and
你不想讓其他物體攻擊它，這跟混搭有關，對吧？
you don't want some other object to attack it, this has to do with mash-ups, right?
因為你想把你的程式碼借給別人
Because you want to lend out your code to somebody else and
您需要確保它們不會感染您的程式碼。
you want to make sure that they don't infect your code.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：我想加強一切，所以
&gt;&gt; Douglas: I want to strengthen everything, so
如果我可以使我的程式碼足夠強大，我可以與第三方一起執行它，
if I can make my code strong enough that I can run it with third parties,
這就是我們希望混搭能夠做到的事情，
which is the thing that we want mash-ups to be able to do,
我可以確信，它也會與我的同事的東西一起工作，那就是
I can be confident that it's going to work with my coworkers stuff as well that That
大多數破壞我們系統的攻擊都是自己造成的。
most of the attacks that are bringing our systems down are self-inflicted right.
我們對自己做的事情，因為我們沒有讓它很好地工作。
The stuff that we do to ourselves because we just didn't get it working well.
&gt；&gt；演講者3：因為你不是說如果你不做混搭，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Because you're not saying if you're not doing mash-ups,
不用擔心這個嗎？
don't worry about this?
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：不，不，我們需要一直擔心這個問題。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: No, no we need to worry about this all the time.
我們寫的每一件事都應該達到這樣的質量水平，所有的東西，所有的東西。
Everything we write should be to that level of quality, everything, everything.